# GREEN LE

ohheygreen.com



linkedin.com/in/dieplegreen



legreen114@gmail.com



+1 519-781-8788



With a comprehensive knowledge in UX/UI Design and 5 years of experience in Content Marketing, Research and Data Analysis, I bring a perfect combination of design thinking approach, sharp business mindset and excellent communication skills through intuitive products as well as valuable experiences I have created for a number of people around the world.

## EXPERIENCE

- **UX Researcher (Placement)** Glen Dimplex Americas, Ontario, 1/2020 - now
- **Online Visual Merchandiser** OnPoint e-Commerce, Vietnam, 2018 - 19
- **Content Specialist** Chopp Ltd. Vietnam, 2017 - 18
- **Digital Media Executive** VIP Worldwide, United Kingdom, 2015 - 16
- **Product Marketing** QUp World Inc, Vietnam, 2013 - 14

- Conduct user research for Canada and US fireplace markets; build user personas; capture insights, analyze consumer data for 5 electric brands in a 3-member team.
- Designed campaign microsite wireframes; conducted website audit; tested mockups, prototype for 6 e-Commerce stores of Unicharm Corp.
- · Collaborated with members in Business Dev, Customer Service, Media, Logistics to manage campaigns on 5 e-Commerce platforms.
- · Consulted clients, enterprise sellers in user experience best practices for their e-Commerce store visual design.
- Established Content Guideline, creative direction and campaign templates.
- Analysed social data/metrics, insights, best practices for 3 luxurious hotels
- Designed online marketing materials for social media campaigns.
- Developed sketches, wireframes, prototypes, user flow for QUp Taxi and other SaaS projects.

## SKILL SET

### This is me!

#### UX / UI Design

Market & User Research, User Interview, Usability Testing, Information Architecture, Wireframing, Rapid Prototyping, UI/ Graphic/ Web Design.

#### Marketing

Data Analysis, Social & Digital Marketing, e-Commerce Merchandising, Client Management, Project Management,

#### **% TOOLS**

Design Marketing Adobe XD Google Analytics Figma Google Suite Invision Microsoft Office Marvel Hootsuite Photoshop Sprout Social Illustrator Trello HTML/ CSS

## EDUCATION

Post-grad, Interaction Design Conestoga College, ON, CA \*GPA: 3.85

MSc., Advertising & Marketing Hull University Business School, UK \*Graduated with Distinction

## © GLOBAL VOLUNTEER

- · Course Lead EF Education First, US, Australia and Singapore (2016 - 17).
- International Delegate JENESYS Economics, Tokyo & Osaka, Japan (2016).
- Course Representative Hull University Business School, UK (2014 - 16).

## PERSONALITY

- A self-motivated collaborator who really enjoys 360 feedback.
- · Highly organized with "spread-sheet thinking".
- Embrace experimentation and initiatives, "fail fast and learn faster".